<resources>
    <string name="war_hint">Use this screen to build a war hit list! Search and select your enemy squad, and enter details about start and outposts.</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">949743418545844</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb949743418545844</string>

    <string name="app_name">SWC Tools</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Strings related to Settings -->

    <!-- Example General settings -->
    <string name="pref_header_general">General</string>

    <string name="pref_title_social_recommendations">Enable social recommendations</string>
    <string name="pref_description_social_recommendations">Recommendations for people to contact
        based on your message history
    </string>

    <string name="pref_title_display_name">Display name</string>
    <string name="pref_default_display_name">John Smith</string>

    <string name="pref_title_add_friends_to_messages">Add friends to messages</string>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_titles">
        <item>Always</item>
        <item>When possible</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="war_outpost_options">
        <item>Outpost</item>
        <item>No Outpost</item>
    </string-array>


    <!-- Example settings for Data & Sync -->
    <string name="pref_header_data_sync">Data &amp; sync</string>

    <string name="pref_title_sync_frequency">Sync frequency</string>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_titles">
        <item>15 minutes</item>
        <item>30 minutes</item>
        <item>1 hour</item>
        <item>3 hours</item>
        <item>6 hours</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_values">
        <item>15</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>60</item>
        <item>180</item>
        <item>360</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="list_preference_entries">
        <item>Entry 1</item>
        <item>Entry 2</item>
        <item>Entry 3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="list_preference_entry_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="multi_select_list_preference_default_value" />

    <string name="pref_title_system_sync_settings">System sync settings</string>

    <!-- Example settings for Notifications -->
    <string name="pref_header_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_new_message_notifications">New message notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_ringtone">Ringtone</string>
    <string name="pref_ringtone_silent">Silent</string>

    <string name="pref_title_vibrate">Vibrate</string>
    <string name="saveButton">Save</string>
    <string name="clearButton">Clear</string>
    <string name="playerIdLabel">Player Id</string>
    <string name="playerSecretLabel">Player Secret</string>
    <string name="addPlayerInstructions">Fill in your player Id and secret below</string>
    <string name="selectFileTxt">Select File</string>
    <string name="importFrom">Import Player Details From Sigma\'s Layout Manager App</string>
    <string name="importSigma">Import Sigma\'s LM Config</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="add_player">Add Player</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="players">Players</string>
    <string name="support">Support</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="text_favorites">Favorites</string>
    <string name="text_schedules">Schedules</string>
    <string name="text_music">Music</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="pulldownrefresh">Pull down to refresh</string>
    <string name="title_activity_player">PlayerActivity</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">SWC ANDROID TOOLS</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle"> (TheMob) | Line: ddavecmo</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>

    <string name="migrate_images_intro">To improve performance, layout images will be migrated from the internal application database to your device storage. Click on the button below to begin.
</string>
    <string-array name="factions">
        <item>- Select Faction - </item>
        <item>Rebel</item>
        <item>Empire</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="layout_favourite_types">
        <item>All Favourites</item>
        <item>Player Favourites</item>
        <item>Last Used</item>
        <item>Most Used</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="save_layout_intro">
        Give your layout a name (any name!) to save it. Use the other options to help organise your layouts if you have many or you just like to organise your stuff.
    </string>
    <string name="none_prompt">None</string>

    <string name="drawer_import">Import Layout</string>
    <string name="drawer_layout_manager">Layout Manager</string>
    <string name="drawer_warlist">War Sign Up</string>
    <string name="drawer_about">About</string>
    <string name="drawer_say_thanks"></string>
    <string name="drawer_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="thanks_text">
        <![CDATA[<p>This app is provided free to use for imperial villains and rebel scum alike :)  It has been a fun journey for me, learning a lot about Android App Development, and I genuinely hope you enjoy the results.</p>
        <p>Building this app has always been about continuing Sigma’s work for the community, hopefully reaching more players with it and an opportunity to build an Android App that had some chance of a user base that could provide me with useful feedback. So, thank you to all that have reported bugs and issues, and made suggestions! Please continue to do so.</p>
<p>If you would like to say thanks, you can drop me message on LINE. If you would like to donate something, please offer to support the hosting costs for KSOD/GSOW.</p>]]></string>

    <string name="about_1">First of all I have to thank and recognise Sigma582 - the player that created the original Layout Manager and Defence tracker tools. Without his work, I wouldn’t have been inspired to create this app. He and others did a lot to demystify how to communicate with Disney\'s server and although he is no longer in the game, I felt it right to thank him here.</string>

    <string name="fund_me_link">https://www.gofundme.com/buy-sf-a-beer</string>
    <string name="about_2">In future releases I will be introducing automatic defence log notifications, and the ability to set your armoury items.</string>
    <string-array name="long_date_formats">
        <item>dd-MMM-yyyy HH:mm:ss</item>
        <item>MMM-dd-yyyy HH:mm:ss</item>
        <item>yyyy-MMM-dd HH:mm:ss</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="short_date_formats">
        <item>dd-MMM-yyyy</item>
        <item>MMM-dd-yyyy</item>
        <item>yyyy-MMM-dd</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="yesno">
        <item>Any</item>
        <item>Yes</item>
        <item>No</item>
    </string-array>




    <string name="settings_date_hint">Change the format of the dates shown on the defence log and on layout manager cards.</string>
    <string name="settings_notifications_hint">Defence Tracker will periodically fetch your latest player data to display a notification detailing the status of your squad center, your protection status and a list of the most recent battles.</string>
    <string name="settings_danger_zone">Only change these settings if you know what you are doing!</string>
    <string name="settings_server_hint">The address the app uses to send the requests to. Only change this if you know this has been changed by Disney.</string>
    <string name="settings_timeout_hint">Set the length of time between requests before the bot re authenticates with the server. Reduce the time if you are finding data refreshes don’t reflect your actual player data.</string>
    <string name="manage_type_tag_hint_text">Add, edit or delete your layout types and tags using the controls below. Swipe left or right to switch views between types and tags.</string>
    <string name="settings_bot_hint">Some data is fetched by using a ‘Bot’ account. Set the bot account details here. (WARNING setting this incorrectly will definitely break the app!).</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings2">Settings</string>

    <string name="player_favourite_layout_hint">Use this tab to view your favourite, most used or last used layouts and quickly apply them to this player from here. </string>
    <string name="player_last_layout_hint">Quickly apply one of your LAST used layouts for this player below (sorted in order of most to least used): </string>
    <string name="getting_started_title">Welcome to the SWC Tools for Android app!</string>
    <string name="getting_started_intro">This app, inspired by the great Sigma582 who created the original Windows versions of Layout Manager and Defence Tracker, allows you to save and quickly swap between layouts on your war and pvp base, as well as keep tabs on your defence status.</string>
    <string name="getting_started_quickstart_title">Getting Started</string>
    <string name="getting_started_youtube">Need a little help getting started? Check out this awesome video from the legend that is Agent Simr which takes you through all you need to get up and running. Huge thanks to him and all that helped him.</string>
    <string name="getting_started_quickstart_1">Click on the plus icon in the bottom right to add a player (app supports unlimited number of players - looking at you, Dennis)</string>
    <string name="c">a192</string>
    <string name="getting_started_quickstart_2">Added players will appear as cards on this screen. Tap on them to view your player status and defence log. Quick saving of layouts is now supported via a menu on the each player card.</string>
    <string name="getting_started_quickstart_3">The main menu is accessible by swiping out from the left from this screen. There you\'ll find tools to import layout files, settings, defence tracker and help/FAQ</string>
    <string name="getting_started_tellmemore_title">Tell me more!</string>
    <string name="getting_started_tellmemore_1">This app needs your Player ID and Player Secret to work, and if you have not previously used the Windows version of Layout Manager you will need to go through a few steps to get this information.</string>
    <string name="getting_started_tellmemore_2">Thankfully, the SWC community is full of awesome people like Agent Simr who produced a YouTube video taking you through how to get your secret, how to use Sigma\'s original tools for Windows PCs, and some of the main features of this app.</string>
    <string name="getting_started_tellmemore_link">LINK!</string>
    <string name="getting_started_tellmemore_3">Head on over to YouTube, watch the video, and give him a thumbs up and a subscribe whilst you\'re there. His videos are legendary amongst the Line Community and it\'s awesome he\'s made one to help people get up and running with all these tools to make our SWC lives a little more bearable. And if you see him about in chats, don\'t forget to thank him!</string>
    <string name="getting_started_tellmemore_4">Some of the actions this app takes will count as you logging into the game (and could trigger heroic defence timers, etc). To help highlight what will count as a log in, buttons are colour coded as follows:</string>
    <string name="getting_started_tellmemore_5">If you have any other questions, you can find a FAQ and help section in the main menu by swiping out from the left.</string>
    <string name="getting_started_signoff">Lastly, I hope you enjoy using this app and imperial or rebel, MTFBWY!</string>
    <string name="button_key_login">This button will log your player in and may trigger the HD timer.</string>
    <string name="button_key_bot">This button uses the BOT to fetch data and will not log your actual player in.</string>
    <string name="button_key_appaction">This button performs some action within the app, like saving data. No request is sent to Disney\'s server here.</string>
    <string name="button_key_minoraction">This button performs some minor action within the app, like editing data. No request is sent to Disney\'s server here.</string>
    <string name="layout_img_setting_hint">Set default for layout images displayed on Layout Manager screen</string>
    <string name="setting_remember_favourite_pref">Enable to remember which option to display on the player layout card by default.</string>
    <string name="my_call_sign">Dave</string>
    <string name="title_activity_update_data">UpdateDataActivity</string>
    <string name="player_details_expanded_hint">Tap lock to expand/collapse by default</string>
    <string name="player_details_expand_row_hint">Tap above to expand the row for more detail</string>
    <string name="title_activity_war_dashboard">WarDashboard</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">Tab 3</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="conflict_refresh_hint">Refreshing your conflict data will log your actual player in and trigger any timers (such as HD).</string>

    <string name="title_activity_layout">LayoutActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_player_config">PlayerConfig</string>
    <string name="deviceidhelptext">Device Id generated automatically by this APP to authenticate you with game servers. </string>
    <string name="setting_logmsgshint">Log all sent and received data from SWC Game servers in the app. Recommend only using this if you need to debug. </string>
    <string name="o">11e4</string>
    <string name="title_activity_edit_layout_json">EditLayoutJsonActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="warsignup_example">"WAR! vs. TheMidnightMob\n\n"
"OUTPOSTS:\n"
"----------\n"
"NO OUTPOST WAR\n\n"
"BASES (HQ - Strength) \n"
"-------------------\n"
"ginerik (11: 3318) -\n"
"Aschro1 (11: 3310) -\n"
"Gshawner (11: 3292) -\n"
"Obi Pepporoni (11: 3284) -\n"
"PegWarrior (11: 3279) -\n"
"Gadalya (11: 3270) -\n"
"Midget Al (11: 3269) -\n"
"Tornado (11: 3266) -\n"
"Vincent'sRebels (11: 3266) -\n"
"PigsNzen (11: 3261) -\n"
"Dave (11: 3260) -\n"
"Snow Weasel (11: 3248) -\n"
"Jigawatt (11: 3239) -\n"
"OGA (11: 3238) -\n"
"Talonore (11: 2985) -\n"
</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_version310">Version310</string>
    <string name="title_activity_layout_detail">LayoutDetail</string>
    <string name="title_activity_multi_image_picker">Choose Images</string>

    <string name="title_activity_full_screen_image">FullScreenImage</string>
    <string name="title_activity_image_gallery">ImageGalleryActivity</string>
    <string name="imagePickerHelp">Tap on an image to add a description. Long press to enter selection mode and delete any unwanted images.</string>
    <string name="layout_image_hint">Tap on an image to enlarge</string>
    <string name="drawer_logs">Logs</string>
    <string name="wiki_git_link">https://github.com/DaveCMo/Android-SWC-Tools/wiki</string>
    <string name="youtubelink">https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLOZarPU-nKm8k7ETeYClrz2l9XDaNdQd-</string>
    <string name="contactinfo">LINE: ddavecmo \nEmail: sfone.swctools@gmail.com</string>

    <string name="title_activity_v4_welcome">V4WelcomeActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_version4_setup">Version4Setup</string>
    <string name="title_activity_release_notes">ReleaseNotesActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_war_attacks">WarAttacks</string>
    <string name="testvalue" />
    <string name="longdateexample">17-Aug-2019 04:08:19</string>
    <string name="wartroopdisclaimer">Important note: this only shows the troops in the attacker\' s transports, hero command and air command, and which of their droids were \'live\' during the attack. It is not possible to confirm which troops were deployed, or what was in the attacker\'s SC.</string>
    <string name="savelayoutlabel">Save layout</string>
    <string name="wardashdisclaimer">"Important note: This Dashboard uses the player account you select to log in and retrieve the data displayed here. \n\n"
        "This means it could trigger heroic defence timers, or even kick you out of any active session you have on another device. \n\n"
        "I.e., don’t be attacking on another device when you click the blue button!"</string>
    <string name="naughtmessage1">"You have attempted to load a player ID that does not belong to you. This is an unethical use of the layout manager app and that ID has been deleted from your app."</string>
    <string name="naughtmessage2"> "Your account details have been logged and the owner of that player ID has been notified."</string>
    <string name="naughtmessage3">"If you attempt to load that player ID again your own player ID will be banned and you will no long be able to use layout manager."</string>
    <string name="set_pvp_button">SET PVP</string>
    <string name="set_war_button">SET WAR</string>
    <string name="title_activity_armoury_equipment_activity">armoury_equipment_activity</string>


</resources>
